That's where heaven will be.
This location is Cape Canaveral.
Kennedy Space Center.
Ermes!
In the beginning of all matter,
there was gravity.
My right hand!
Jolyne Cujoh!
So you are the one who's been
helping Jolyne this whole time.
We have to stay away from his attacks!
Anything that touches its fist
turns inside out.
I don't know its range,
but it makes everything fall sideways!
So that's how the weak gravity
at Cape Canaveral
affected and evolved the priest's Stand!
To achieve happiness,
humans must bear a curse,
and overcome fate.
The trial Dio and I had to overcome
was Joestar's bloodline.
Her heart was turned inside out.
It's the phone!
It didn't have a signal a moment ago.
Could this be…
Jolyne is alive.
She's alive, but just barely.
Mr. Jotaro!
He's nearby!
Anastasia, find Jolyne!
Jolyne isn't dead!
What?
What did you do, Jolyne Cujoh?
Your heart was turned inside out!
We must settle the score.
The Joestar bloodline must be overcome!
Where are you going?
The best way to protect Jolyne
is to kill that priest!
EPISODE 35: SEE MOON (2)
Jolyne… I sense she is
in no condition to move.
How did she survive?
Could it be that I missed her vitals?
No.
Without a doubt,
my Stand struck her heart.
I was certain of it.
Could it be Joestar's blood,
the bloodline of Kujo?
Is it getting in the way of Dio and me,
once again?
I absolutely must finish off
Jolyne Cujoh here.
Both in prison and in Orlando,
Jolyne Cujoh interfered.
She's a trial that I must overcome
to achieve my purpose.
Have confidence, Father Pucchi.
Fate will choose to side with me.
Dio and I have a purpose much grander
than their pitiful sense of justice.
Not a single human can hinder my plans!
Hey you…
Call a doctor.
What happened to my hip bone?
Help me!
I'm close. I'm very close.
Jolyne Cujoh fell near here.
She's here.
That's a piece of Jolyne's clothing.
Jolyne went inside this building.
By the way, do not come
a single step closer to me.
Stand back.
I don't even count you as an obstacle.
Retreat, See Moon!
That man is not Anastasia!
Diver Drive can submerge in more places
than just the walls or the ground.
I found a tourist who died
from your gravity ability,
and changed his bone structure
to match mine.
You're already within my range.
Take this! Diver Drive!
I missed!
He turned his own face inside out.
To me, you're merely a pesky fly
I can easily swat away.
She touched my face.
That was Jolyne Cujoh's hand.
She's on the move.
What is she planning to do?
How is she able to move?
That's blood.
She is wounded, without a doubt.
My heart tells me to track her down,
no matter what.
I will end her, right here and now!
Jotaro Kujo will be here any minute
to rescue Jolyne Cujoh.
If Anastasia rejoins the fight,
the battle will be difficult.
Jolyne Cujoh's allies are headed this way
in hopes to save her life.
Hence it is now,
I must vanquish you, once and for all.
Your death
shall crush the resolve and hopes
of your allies who have gathered here.
Especially Jotaro,
who will lose his daughter.
His purpose and resolve in life
shall vanish along with Jolyne.
He will no longer be a match
for Dio and me.
I must finish her off, here and now!
I will find you, no matter the cost!
Come out, Jolyne Cujoh!
Show yourself!
Jolyne Cujoh!
It's only her thread.
Dammit, she's behind me!
I will give it my all
to kill you right here!
I know that you are wounded!
I am the center of gravity,
so if I turn my body upside down,
everything will fall toward my feet.
See Moon!
Both strikes landed!
Both your arms are now useless!
Those strange shapes…
Why didn't her arms turn inside out?
How could this be?
Show yourself, Jolyne Cujoh!
You cannot run from your fate!
What is that thing?
What is that?
What's the shape of that thing,
where her heart should be?
Stone Ocean!
Mobius strips?
Is that what you're creating?
STAND NAME: STONE OCEAN
STAND MASTER: JOLYNE CUJOH
Start tracing its surface with a finger,
and keep going.
Follow the surface
without lifting the finger.
Before long, you have traced both sides.
You will be back at your starting point.
This non-orientable shape
was discovered in the 19th century
by a German mathematician.
It is called "Mobius strip,"
after his name.
The back side exists
only if there is a front side.
If there's no front and back,
there's no turning inside out.
A non-orientable infinity strip
can be made with thread!
Is that what she created?
Did she make a Mobius strip
the instant she was struck?
I admire the first human
who tried to eat mushrooms.
They risked poisoning themselves.
Was he a fool who happened to get lucky?
Otherwise,
was the discovery driven
by his desperate starvation?
Would you survive if I strike your head?
A single hit will do.
Which angle would be best?
A single hit to the head is all it takes.
Is this all you've got?
I'm disappointed.
Come at me with everything you got!
No.
I'm waiting for a definitive moment.
I've been circling you, containing myself.
I'm waiting for
the perfect moment to strike.
Do you understand?
The more I walk around,
the more these objects fall.
That's why I'm waiting.
I'm waiting for victory
to fall into my hands.
Do you understand?
Is your Mobius strip enough to save you,
considering your wounds?
There it is.
The chance I've been waiting for!
A security officer's corpse!
It's in my hand!
Jolyne!
- Shit!
- Whoa!
Dammit.
Jolyne!
What?
The Speedwagon Foundation
shot this harpoon from the sky
three kilometers above.
It was aimed to land
on the Visitor Center's premises.
I made a copy of it with my sticker,
and duplicated the harpoon.
When the sticker is removed,
the copy flies back to the original.
I clung on to the harpoon,
so that despite your gravity,
I can be pulled up here in an instant.
Then, I used my Stand
to break it into pieces.
We came to this spot
where he felt her presence.
Dad…
Jotaro Kujo and Ermes!
You're surrounded, Father Pucchi.
Completing your Stand in 36 hours
was just your wishful thinking.
It's over.
You have no allies left.
You will be defeated before
the new moon arrives!
You're mistaken, Emporio.
As I thought, fate…
gives me trials, yet sides with me.
The ones who will aid me
in attaining my powers
are the Joestar descendants!
After being stuck under
this steel framing,
I now understand!
My allies were the Kujos all along!
What the hell?
He's rising up towards the sky!
I am the center of gravity.
I understand now, Dio!
This is the answer.
I have no need to wait another 36 hours
for the new moon to arrive.
I need the gravitational force
of the new moon.
Then I'll just float higher in the sky
and find an area
with equal gravitational pull.
I'll put myself where there is gravity
equal to that of the new moon!
There must be an exact spot
that can complete See Moon's power!
You think we'll let you get away?
You don't know when to surrender, do you?
Stay calm, look for the exact location.
Count the prime numbers
and maintain my composure.
- Thirteen, seventeen…
- That bastard is muttering something!
Gravity hasn't changed!
It's still pulling us sideways.
Ermes, look to your right.
Pick up the gun he dropped.
You've grown, Jolyne.
Hold onto the guardrails.
Ermes,
pick up the gun and shoot him.
See Moon!
Star Platinum: The World!
You wish to use your Stand
to deflect the bullets.
Time can stay stopped for
a maximum of five seconds.
You will not see this harpoon.
Once the time starts again,
the harpoon will impale you.
Three seconds.
Two seconds.
One second.
Time will now start.
What just happened?
The harpoon missed.
He dodged during my time stop.
That priest…
He's unharmed.
He's opening the hatch.
It looks like he's trying to board it.
The Space Shuttle is in the air!
The priest is inside
the exhibition Shuttle!
He dodged the harpoon, but how?
Damn…
he's not only trying to get away.
Don't tell me…
he learned something
that he shouldn't have,
a condition that will allow him
to complete his Stand!
It is you who brought
this Pucchi to heaven.
All this time, even in prison,
my allies were you.
Father in heaven,
guide me!
Watch over me,
that I shall not stray from my path.
I give myself to thee!
Yes, I feel it!
The position! It's here!
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter